<resources>
    <string name="app_name" translatable="false">GeekBrainsWeather</string>
    <string name="enter_city_name">Enter city name:</string>
    <string name="humidity">Humidity</string>
    <string name="air_pressure">Air Pressure</string>
    <string name="wind_speed">Wind Speed</string>
    <string name="check_weather">Check weather</string>
    <string name="available_cities" translatable="false">Available cities: Moscow, London, Paris.</string>
    <string name="city_info">Moscow is the major political, economic, cultural, and scientific center
        of Russia and Eastern Europe, as well as the largest city (both by population and by area)
        entirely on the European continent. By broader definitions, Moscow is among the world\'s
        largest cities, being the 14th largest metro area, the 18th largest agglomeration, the 14th
        largest urban area, and the 11th largest by population within city limits worldwide.
        According to Forbes 2013, Moscow has been ranked as the ninth most expensive city in the
        world by Mercer and has one of the world\'s largest urban economies, being ranked as an alpha
        global city according to the Globalization and World Cities Research Network, and is also one
        of the fastest growing tourist destinations in the world according to the MasterCard Global
        Destination Cities Index.Moscow is the northernmost and coldest megacity on Earth.
        It is home to the Ostankino Tower, the
        tallest free standing structure in Europe; the Federation Tower, the second-tallest skyscraper
        in Europe; and the Moscow International Business Center. By its territorial expansion on
        July 1, 2012 southwest into the Moscow Oblast, the area of the capital more than doubled,
        going from 1,091 to 2,511 square kilometers (421 to 970 sq mi), resulting in Moscow becoming
        the largest city on the European continent by area; it also gained an additional population
        of 233,000 people.Moscow is situated on the Moskva River in the Central Federal
        District of European Russia, making it
        Europe\'s most populated inland city. The city is well known for its architecture,
        particularly its historic buildings such as Saint Basil\'s Cathedral in Russian architectural
        style with a richly decorated and multicolored facade. With over 40 percent of its
        territory covered by greenery, it is one of the greenest capitals and major cities in Europe
        and the world, having the largest forest in an urban area within its borders—more than any
        other major city—even before its expansion in 2012. The city has served as the capital of a
        progression of states, from the medieval Grand Duchy of Moscow and the subsequent Tsardom of
        Russia to the Russian Empire to the Soviet Union and the contemporary Russian Federation.</string>

</resources>
